<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EA Loans</string>
    <string name="web">You must be familiar and have interacted with many websites in your day to
        day activities. Earning through websites is simple. It just requires your time and patience and in a few days, your success will be knocking at your
    door. \nThe first thing to do is have a website: If you are a developer, this is easy for you and you are not, then find a developer who
    work on your website. Once you do this, create ad spaces on your website. These will be used to show and play ds. Use google admob to run ads in your website.
    You can create a website that sells products, services or just gives information to the users. If you want to engage user frequently, check out blogs.
    Blogs promote reader engagement i.e Readers have a chance to comment and voice their different concerns and thoughts to the community.</string>
    <string name="blog">A blog is an online journal or informational website displaying information in reverse chronological order, with the latest posts appearing first, at the top.
        It is a platform where a writer or a group of writers share their views on an individual subject.
    There are many reasons to start a blog for personal use and only a handful of strong ones for business blogging. Blogging for business, projects, or anything else that
        might bring you money has a very straightforward purpose
    .The more frequent and better your blog posts are, the higher the chances for your website to get discovered and visited by your target audience. This means that a blog is an effective lead generation tool. Add a great call to action (CTA) to your content, and it will convert your website traffic into high-quality leads.
        A blog also allows you to showcase your niche authority and build a brand. The main difference between a blog and a website is Blogs need frequent updates.</string>
    <string name="broker">An insurance broker sells, solicits, or negotiates insurance for compensation.
    An insurance broker is a professional who represents consumers in their search for the best insurance policy for their needs. They work closely with their clients to research coverage, terms, conditions, and price and then recommend the insurance policy that best fits the bill.
        Unlike captive and independent agents, who represent one or more insurance companies, a broker’s primary duty is to the client.\n
     Most commissions are between 2 and 8% of premiums, depending on state regulations. Brokers sell all types of insurance, including health insurance, homeowner insurance, accident insurance, life insurance, and annuities.</string>
    <string name="agent">An insurance agent is a professional who sells an insurance company’s products to consumers for a commission. An agent helps consumers select the right insurance to buy, but represents the insurance company in the transaction.
        \nThere are two types of insurance agents:
        Captive agents typically represent only one insurer.\n
        Independent insurance agents typically represent more than one insurer.\n
        Both captive and independent agents work on commission and can execute an insurance transaction from start to finish.\n
     agent might earn a 15 percent commission on general liability policies and a 10 percent commission on workers compensation policies. If your purchases a liability policy for a $2,000 premium, you will collect $2,000 from him/her, retain $300 in commission, and send the remaining $1,700 to your insurance company.</string>
    <string name="social">Social media marketing is the use of social media platforms to connect with your audience to build your brand, increase sales, and drive website traffic.
        The major social media platforms (at the moment) are Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, LinkedIn, Pinterest, YouTube, and Snapchat.
    This involves publishing great content on your social media profiles, listening to and engaging your followers, analyzing your results, and running social media advertisements.
    Publishing to social media is as simple as sharing a blog post, an image, or a video on a social media platform. It’s just like how you would share on your personal Facebook profile. But you will want to plan your content ahead of time instead of creating and publishing content spontaneously. Also, to ensure that you are maximizing your reach on social media, you need to publish great content that your audience likes, at the right timing and frequency.</string>
    <string name="affiliate">Affiliate marketing is the process of earning a commission by promoting other peoples or companys products. You find a product you like, promote it to others and earn a piece of the profit for each sale that you make.\n
    It is based on revenue sharing. If you have no product and want to make money, then you can promote a product that you feel has value and earn an income from it as an affiliate marketer.
    affiliate marketing can be seen as the process of spreading product creation and product marketing across different parties, where each party receives a share of the revenue according to their contribution.It’s not just the promotion or just the product creation that defines who you are as an affiliate marketer.
        You can be both the creator and the marketer and still profit from the underlying idea of sharing revenue.</string>
    <string name="bitcoin">Cryptocurrency is the new trend in the financial market at the moment. We are talking about bitcoin. Its value is constantly rising
    day in day out. This is a good indicator that investing in bitcoin is worth it. There are several sites one can trade in eg Paxful.
    The good about this is, you do not need $1000 to start trading. You can start with as little as $10 but its advisable to start with $100.
    With this amount, you can make your $10 profit everyday buying and selling bitcoin. Just register you account and start buying and selling.
    Bitcoin uses peer-to-peer technology to operate with no central authority or banks managing transactions and the issuing of bitcoins is carried out collectively by the network. Bitcoin is open-source its design is public, nobody owns or controls Bitcoin and everyone can take part.
    Digital money thats instant, private, and free from bank fees. Download your desired wallet app and start using Bitcoin today.</string>
    <string name="newt">newt</string>
    <string name="freebitcoin">Shop Online and Earn Bitcoin\n
You can do more with bitcoin online than simply purchase things.
        You can also use your everyday shopping experiences to increase your bitcoin account. How?\n
    \n
    Open a Crypto Interest Account to Earn Free Bitcoin\n
A lot of crypto investors buy Bitcoin as a long-term investment,
        only to find out that there isnt much else they can do to grow their overall holdings.
        Let your cryptocurrency do all the work by earning free crypto in the form of interest
        by storing it in a BlockFi Interest Account (BIA).
        Of course, the big question is how much interest can you earn?\n
    \n
    Start Crypto Mining to Earn Bitcoin
Crypto mining is another path to earning bitcoin online. But whats crypto mining? Miners are the back-bone of the blockchain.
        Using specialized hardware, they complete complex calculations in order to confirm and facilitate the exchange of
        value over the blockchain. Miners test the validity of each transaction by subjecting it to a sophisticated
        cryptographic puzzle and submitting it for other miners to confirm and come to a
        trustless consensus on each transaction that hits the blockchain.</string>
    <string name="ecommerce">eCommerce sites have exploded in popularity in recent years. With the prevalence of platforms like WordPress and WooCommerce, creating an eCommerce site couldn’t be easier.\n
    There are two different methods of running a successful online store:\n
Creating and selling a niche physical product to a dedicated group of buyers\n
Purchasing cheaper goods manufactured in foreign countries, repackaging them, and selling them at a markup.\n
    The first approach can be very successful, but it does require a passion for the product and the willingness to do a ton of research, product development, and testing.
    \nIf the first approach seems a little risky for your first online business, then you might consider the second option of reselling popular overseas products. This method involves sourcing a popular product from a platform like AliExpress,
        repacking the product, and selling it through your own storefront.</string>
    <string name="digital">It seems like digital courses are everywhere today. So, if you have valuable knowledge that someone would pay for, this could be a great opportunity.\n
In addition to having your own courses, learning platforms such as BitDegree offer a chance to become an instructor.
        Its a unique opportunity to pass your skills and experience to thousands of people who are eager to learn something new.\n
    Digital courses can be produced in a lot of different formats, from simple PDF downloads, all the way up to self-produced video courses that have dozens of hours of content.
    \nIf you’re looking to create a digital course, but haven’t settled on your topic, its a good idea to poll your audience. Often, they can tell you exactly what they’d like to learn and would be willing to pay for.
    \nLike most other methods on this list, digital courses can be integrated into most styles of websites including blogs,
        eCommerce platforms, and even affiliate marketing sites.</string>
    <string name="membership">Membership sites have exploded in popularity recently and the idea is easy enough to implement. It does, however, require having an existing audience of some sort.\n
For example, Mark Manson runs a popular self-development blog. On his site, there’s a membership portion that gives users access to online courses, videos, and additional article commentary.
        For fans of his work, it’s a great deal.\n
    People are already visiting your website because they like what you write about and how you use your style.
        So, you can create a membership section of your site that offers premium content. Now, every single person who visits your site won’t take you up on the offer, but your dedicated fans will find it irresistible.
    The type of membership site you create will depend upon the kind of site you run and the level of depth you want to go with your premium content.
    </string>
    <string name="online">Online directories aren’t as popular as they used to be, but they can still be profitable.

They work in a similar fashion to the job board above. But, instead of people paying to post jobs, or get access to the job board, they’ll pay you a monthly fee for a directory listing.
    \nIf you have an authoritative site or get a lot of traffic, then these listings are pretty valuable.

Lets say you run a site thats dedicated to web development and design. You produce high-quality content and have a solid amount of authority. You could create a directory portion of your site where web developers and agencies can purchase a listing.

This will not only provide them with a solid authoritative backlink, but it could be a nice source of traffic for their business.
    Usually, directories work by charging a monthly subscription fee to be listed. You could even charge a premium fee to let businesses list themselves at the top of the directory,
        getting even more eyes on their listing.</string>
    <string name="buysell">The process of buying and selling websites is like the process of flipping homes — you buy a house that has investment potential,
        fix it up, and sell it for a higher profit.\n
    The process is pretty straightforward. But, just know that there are risks involved.
        So, dont invest money in a site you can’t afford to lose.\n
    Here’s how you buy and sell sites for a profit:\n
You find an undervalued website that you know you can improve. For this, check out marketplaces like EmpireFlippers,
        Flippa, and We Sell Your Site.\n
    Do your research to uncover revenue and traffic numbers, link profiles, and the real reason why someone is selling the site.\n
    If everything checks out, purchase the site.\n
    Make site improvements to maximize its traffic and revenue.\n
        Sell the site for a better profit.</string>
    <string name="youtube">YouTube is one of the world’s largest search engines. But, instead of searching for websites, people are looking for entertaining, fun, or informative videos.\n
You can monetize your YouTube channel by using their advertising system or sending your viewers to a website you’ve monetized in another way.
You can think of building a YouTube channel in a similar fashion to creating a website, except you’re creating videos, not written content.
    If you feel comfortable in front of the camera, and want to try your luck creating videos, then you’ll need to figure out what your channel will be about. Typically, there are two types of
        YouTube channels out there that are most successful:\n
    Entertaining content. This style includes content like web series, comedy videos, pranks, reviews, video game walkthroughs, and a lot more.\n
Educational content. This style is more geared towards, “How to” phrases.
        If you have useful skills or information you want to convey through a video, then this is a solid option for you.\n
    Once you’ve decided what kind of channel you’re going to start, it’s time to start creating.</string>
    <string name="program">Learning how to program can be a very valuable skill. Whether you’re looking to freelance with your skills or develop and build your own software.
Once you have enough skills under your belt, you can perform such tasks as building a consumer application,
        a niche web or mobile app, or even a mobile game.
        A lot of very successful businesses have been built on the back of software.\n
    A lot of today’s software is built by larger companies, but, if you look through the Google Play or Apple Store,
        you’ll find that a lot of the most popular apps have been built by people just like you.
    If you’re looking to make money off your own software or apps, here’s an approach you can take:\n

Do market research to uncover what is currently needed the most\n
Build an MVP version of the software\n
Get feedback from initial users and beta testers\n
Integrate feedback and launch the first version of your product\n
Prepare a marketing campaign based on your budget</string>
    <string name="webdev">If you don’t have the development skills, then your first step is to learn how to code. Once you have the skills, it’s time to start finding work.

Create a profile on sites like Upwork and Freelancer, and start pitching jobs to get paid.\n

To increase your chances of success it can be helpful to create a niche for yourself, and craft your profile and portfolio accordingly.\n

For example, maybe you want to build websites for real estate agents and property management companies. Or, you’d like to specialize in creating eCommerce websites that use WooCommerce and WordPress.\n

First, make sure there’s a need for your skills, maybe there are a lot of jobs posted for your specific skillset. Then, craft your niche web development business and start pitching relevant jobs.</string>
    <string name="ig">Instagram is one of the fastest-growing social media platforms out there. However, did you know you can make money directly from Instagram, just by having a big enough following?

It’s becoming more difficult to build a large following on Instagram, but it can be a pretty easy way to earn a nice living online. Large brands and other companies will actually pay you just to do a post about their company, or showcase one of their products.\n

Usually, how much you make per post will depend on the size of your followers, and how engaged they are. You can expect to earn anywhere from a couple hundred to multiple thousands of dollars per post.\n

Building a sizable Instagram audience will take time, but if you love taking photos, don’t mind spending a lot of time on your phone, and are dedicated to posting regularly, then it’s worth a shot.</string>
    <string name="affweb">An affiliate marketing site is built upon recommending or reviewing certain products. Then, when a reader buys that product through your link, you’ll receive a commission.

Although it might not seem like a big revenue generator, there are multi-million dollar sites based on affiliate revenue alone.\n

For example, Wirecutter was so profitable that the New York Times bought the site for $30 million. There is also Lucieslist, a site about baby product reviews and Outdoorgearlab, a site dedicated to camping and hiking gear reviews.\n

To start your own affiliate marketing website, join an affiliate program that fits your site’s niche. For instance, if you have a blog dedicated to computers and technology, you can become a Hostinger affiliate.\n
        After signing up for the Hostinger Affiliate Program, you’ll get access to the affiliate marketing dashboard where you can track all of your campaigns. Then, use the provided marketing materials — like banners, ebooks, and infographics — to increase sales.</string>
    <string name="resellhost">Resell hosting is another great way to make money online.The basic idea of reseller hosting is providing a dedicated server space, which you can use to build your very own web hosting brand. It allows you to:\n

Create cPanel-powered web hosting accounts\n
Set custom resource limits (i.e., disk space, bandwidth)\n
Conveniently manage all accounts using WHM\n
Since cPanel is the most widely used tool when it comes to managing a hosting account, it will be easy to attract new users. The server uptime is also monitored by an in-house administrator team, which ensures stable uptime and availability.

It allows you to focus on user acquisition, rather than the technical aspects of server management. If you’ll have any questions, a dedicated 24/7 support staff will be there to help.

Especially if you’re familiar with how web hosting works, reselling it will be a walk in the park. Who knows, you may become one of the web hosting giants if you put enough effort.</string>
    <string name="board">Job boards can be a rather profitable way to earn a living with your website.

The process is simple — people looking to hire someone in a specific niche will post a job listing on your site and your
        visitors will apply for the job.
    You can either charge people to post job listings. Or, you could charge your visitors a monthly membership fee to access the job board.

Keep in mind that you do need to have decent traffic in order for such a site to work. A company wont pay to post a job on
        your site if you arent sending any qualified applicants their way.</string>
    <string name="your">Selling services from your website is one of the fastest ways to online money making.
    Create a niche blog that contains useful information about a certain topic. Let’s say you have a blog about woodworking techniques, and you’ve built a decent sized email list and got a solid traffic number.

You can add a services page to your site where you offer woodworking lessons, whether in person or through mediums such as Skype.
    \n
    The other method involves creating a WordPress website for the sole purpose of pitching your services to companies and individuals.

Let’s say you want to be a freelance writer. You need to pick a niche and build your website. Then, create a few pages telling people who you are, the services you provide and showcase a few examples of your work.

Then, start generating leads for your new service business by engaging in guest blogging, podcast interviews, or cold outreach.

If you’re looking to take your service-based business to new heights, then combining the two methods will give you great results.</string>
    <string name="survey">Taking online surveys probably isn’t the best way to earn a passive income online.
        But, if you’re looking for some fast cash and prizes, without having to take time to learn a new skill,
        then it could be worth considering.\n

Taking surveys is exactly what it sounds like. You take online surveys and get compensated with cash,
        coupons, prizes, and gift cards.\n
    Usually, you’ll have to give them your demographic info so they can gain information about your background and interests,
        but after that, you can start earning right away.</string>
    <string name="socialma">Most of us are active on social media these days. But, did you know you could earn a living managing social media accounts?

If you’re already an avid social media user, then you’re already one step ahead. It’ll be much easier for you to convey your expertise and convince others to manage their accounts for a fee.

If you’re not, don’t worry. There are a ton of educational resources like the Hootsuite Academy, which will teach you about the ins and outs of social media.
    Once your knowledge is up to speed, it’s time to head back to the freelancing sites like Upwork and Freelancer to start pitching jobs.

If you’re looking to increase your chances of landing clients, you can use what you’ve learned to brand and grow your social media management company.</string>
    <string name="graphic">If you have design skills, or you’ve always loved playing around with Photoshop and Illustrator, then you can use these skills to start making money online.

You can use the freelance platforms mentioned above, create a profile, and start pitching, or you can test your skills on a platform like 99designs. On this site, you’ll compete with other designers for certain projects.
        If the client likes your design, then you’ll get the project and begin working.
    \nAnother way to get clients as a graphic designer is to go offline. Go to your local chamber of commerce, or spend some time walking around your town. Chances are you’ll see plenty of businesses who are in need of your graphic design skills. Whether it’s for a new logo, a brochure, or even company uniforms.

You can try going to your local co-working space. These are usually filled with startups and other companies who are in need of the design skills you have.</string>
    <!--<string name="banner">399424024528292_399425471194814</string>-->
    <!--<string name="interstitial">399424024528292_399433981193963</string>-->


    <string name="banner">IMG_16_9_APP_INSTALL#607402693307934_607717893276414</string>
    <string name="interstitial">IMG_16_9_APP_INSTALL#607402693307934_607763939938476</string>
</resources>
